{
    "subject": "resource/Danilo_Carando",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1988-08-05",
    "human_readable": "Danilo Carando was born on August 5, 1988.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9414618611335754,
            "question": "August 5th of what year marks Danilo Carando's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9234159588813782,
            "question": "Is August 5th a significant date for Danilo Carando?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.905199408531189,
            "question": "On which date was Danilo Carando born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9017840623855591,
            "question": "When was Danilo Carando born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7852023243904114,
            "question": "What is Danilo Carando's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6511438488960266,
            "question": "What month and day was Danilo Carando born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5399305820465088,
            "question": "How old is Danilo Carando as of today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5349901914596558,
            "question": "What is the day and month of Danilo Carando's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45429304242134094,
            "question": "In what year did Danilo Carando come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11570152640342712,
            "question": "Is August a common birth month?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Danilo Carando was born on August 5, 1988.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1353_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Danilo Carando come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1353_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the day and month of Danilo Carando's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1353_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is Danilo Carando as of today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1353_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1353_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Danilo Carando was born on August 5, 1988.\" Both 35.txt and 28.txt specify his date of birth as 05 August 1988 or 5 August 1988, which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}